By RentAnAdviser.com
Is this the real life?
Is this just fantasy?
Caught in a landslide‚ no
escape from reality
Open your eyes‚ look up
to the skies and see
I am just a poor boy‚
I need no sympathy
Because I am easy come‚ easy
go‚ little high‚ little low
Any way the wind blows doesn′t
really matter to me‚ to me
Mama‚ just killed a man
Put a gun against his head
Pulled my trigger‚ now He is dead
Mama‚ life had just begun
But now I have gone and
thrown it all away
Mama‚ ooh‚ didn′t mean to make you cry
If I am not back again
this time tomorrow
Carry on‚ carry on as if
nothing really matters
Too late‚ my time has come
Sends shivers down my spine‚
body′s aching all the time
Goodbye‚ everybody‚ I have got to go
Gotta leave you all behind
and face the truth
Mama‚ ooh‚ I don′t want to die
I sometimes wish I had never
been born at all
I see a little silhouetto of a man
Scaramouche‚ Scaramouche‚
will you do the Fandango
Thunderbolt and lightning‚
very‚ very fright′ning me
(Galileo) Galileo‚ (Galileo) Galileo‚
Galileo figaro magnifico
(I am just a poor boy‚
nobody loves me)
He is just a poor boy
from a poor family
Spare him his life from
this monstrosity
Easy come‚ easy go‚ will
you let me go?
Bismillah! No‚ we will not let you go
(Let him go) Bismillah!
We will not let you go
(Let me go) Will not let you go
(Let me go) Ah‚ no‚ no‚
no‚ no‚ no‚ no‚ no
(Oh mamma mia‚ mamma mia)
Mama mia‚ let me go
Beelzebub has a devil put aside
for me‚ for me‚ for me
So you think you can stone
me and spit in my eye?
So you think you can love
me and leave me to die?
Oh‚ baby‚ can′t do this to me‚ baby!
Just gotta get out‚ just gotta
get right outta here!
Nothing really matters‚ anyone can see
Nothing really matters
Nothing really matters to me
Any way the wind blows
By RentAnAdviser.com